{
    "subject": "resource/Tour_de_France_(song)",
    "predicate": "property/genre",
    "object": "resource/Electronic_music",
    "human_readable": "The genre of the Tour de France song is Electronic music.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.970624566078186,
            "question": "Is the Tour de France song classified as Electronic music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.953551709651947,
            "question": "What genre of music is the Tour de France song?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49442464113235474,
            "question": "Are there any popular songs in the Electronic music genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4642173945903778,
            "question": "What are some popular subgenres within Electronic music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39101824164390564,
            "question": "What other genres of music exist besides Electronic?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3402528166770935,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of Electronic music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30950412154197693,
            "question": "What makes Electronic music unique compared to other genres?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2306164801120758,
            "question": "Can you name a famous electronic music artist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20953918993473053,
            "question": "Can you think of any famous events associated with Electronic music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20825061202049255,
            "question": "How has Electronic music influenced popular culture?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The genre of the Tour de France song is Electronic music.",
            "html": "dbpedia_35_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you think of any famous events associated with Electronic music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_35_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a famous electronic music artist?",
            "html": "dbpedia_35_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes Electronic music unique compared to other genres?",
            "html": "dbpedia_35_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_35_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_35_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_35_137.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_35_147.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_35_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_35_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_35_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_35_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_35_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_35_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention Kraftwerk as a German band known for their experimental electronic music, and that their song \"Tour de France\" is considered a groundbreaking electronic music composition ahead of its time when it was first released in 1983."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that the genre of the Tour de France song by Kraftwerk is electronic music. Specifically, the documents mention that Kraftwerk's work is pioneering in the field of electronic music and refers to their use of synthetic melodies, rhythms, and beats typical of an electronic music composition."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}